imax.com 2017-11-02

# Privacy Policy | IMAX

### Our Commitment to Privacy

IMAX Corporation and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “IMAX” or “we”) value your time, respect your privacy, and seek to earn your trust. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website (the “Website”).

We collect information about you through the Website in an effort to improve your IMAX experience and to tell you about our products, services, contests and promotions. Your trust is essential to us, and we are not in the business of selling or renting information about our customers to others.

In line with these values, our privacy policy may change from time to time. If it does, we will post an updated policy on the Website and change the “last updated” line above. For this reason, we ask that you check periodically to review our policy for such changes.

If you have any unanswered questions about our privacy policy, click this [info@imax.com](mailto:info@imax.com) to reach our Privacy Officer.

### What kind of personal information does IMAX collect?

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, phone number, gender, birthday, and personal interests, when you visit the Website, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, participate in a contest, promotion, or survey, or communicate with us in any other way.

We may collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help identify you, gather broad demographic information about users of the Website, diagnose problems with our systems, and administer the Website.

You represent and warrant that any information you provide to us is your true and correct information.

### How does IMAX collect this information?

We receive and store any information from your visits to the Website or that you give us in any other way.

As is true of most web sites, we gather and store certain information automatically, including IP addresses, browser types, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. This information does not identify individual users, and is used to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

To do this, we use ‘cookies’ or alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features that improve the performance of the Website for you. If you are concerned about cookies, the “help”, “options” or “preferences” functions on most browsers will allow you to limit or disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of our interactive features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

To ensure we are sending our e-mails to the right address, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from us if your computer supports such capabilities.

Last, to provide customer service, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive address information from these sources to correct our records and contact you more easily.

We will correct any personal information we store whenever possible and delete stale information on an ongoing basis and are very happy to hear from you to ensure that our information is as complete and accurate as possible.

### How does IMAX use your personal information?

By submitting personal information and registering on the Website, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be used by IMAX for internal marketing analyses and to provide you with information from time to time about IMAX and IMAX promotions. The customer's contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary and will not be shared with other affiliated companies. Demographic and profile data (such as postal code and age) may be collected at the Website.

We run contests on the Website in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), and demographic information (like their postal code or age). We may use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and will not be shared with other companies or affiliated companies. Only IMAX has access to your personal information.

The information we learn from you helps us personalize and improve your experience on the Website. Only IMAX has access to your personal information.

In particular, by using the Website, you acknowledge and agree that we may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To communicate with you, to send you information about our products, services, contests, and promotions;
  * To administer contests and other promotions;
  * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services;
  * To analyze trends and statistics;
  * To correct our records and make it easier to deliver your next communication more easily;
  * To respond to your requests and to contact you if necessary; and
  * To protect the security and integrity of the Website and our business.

If you have questions or concerns about how we use personal information, please contact us as indicated below.

### Does IMAX share personal information about me?

By using the Website, you agree that we may share your personal information about you to address a security, integrity, or legal threat to the Website or our business, including for fraud protection and to protect the legal rights, privacy or safety of IMAX or our employees, agents and contractors, to enforce our terms of use, to respond to inquiries or requests from government or public authorities in any country in which we operate, including the U.S. and Canada, or to comply with the law or legal process.

### How does IMAX keep your information secure?

IMAX is always striving to ensure you a safe and convenient online experience. This goes beyond our technologies to include physical, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect your personal information. This Website has reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and interception by third parties of personal information. However, security lies in your hands as well. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. We assume no liability for interception, alteration or misuse of information transmitted over the Internet.

### What is "phishing"?

"Phishing" is a scam where fraudsters pretend that they represent well-known companies to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail claiming to be from IMAX that asks you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through e-mail.

### What about links to other web sites?

This Website contains links to third-party web sites. All such sites are independent from the Website and from IMAX. IMAX has no control over and expressly disclaims any liability for such sites or their contents. Our links do not constitute an express or implied adoption or endorsement of anything contained in the other sites. Any transactions that take place between you and the third party are directly with the third party and IMAX shall not be held responsible for any loss or damage that you may incur as a consequence thereto. Please read the privacy policies and terms and conditions posted on these other sites before using the sites or disclosing any personal information to the sites. If you decide to access any of these sites, you do so entirely at your own risk.

This Privacy Policy extends only to data collected on pages hosted on the Website.

### How do I contact you?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Website, or your dealings with the Website, you can contact us via the e-mail address [‘info@imax.com’](mailto:info@imax.com) or by writing to IMAX Privacy Officer, 2525 Speakman Drive, Mississauga, Ontario, Canada L5K1B1.

_____________________________________________________________

_The below Privacy Policy is specific to the United Kingdom_

Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to Privacy

IMAX Corporation (of 12582 West Millennium Drive, Los Angeles, California 90094) and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “IMAX” or “we”) value your time, respect your privacy, and seek to earn your trust. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. It sets out how we collect personal information about you (such as your name, address, email and telephone details) and how that information, together with any other personal information that you provide to us, may be used by us. By providing us with personal information you are deemed to have accepted the terms of this policy. Please do not provide us with any personal information if you do not agree to the terms of this policy.

You can contact us via the e-mail address [info@imax.com](mailto:info@imax.com) or by writing to IMAX Privacy Officer, 2525 Speakman Drive, Mississauga, Ontario, Canada L5K1B1.

**What personal information may we collect from you?**

### We may collect the following personal information from you:

  * Personal information that you provide through the registration procedure on the website. We need this information to make sure that you can enjoy all the benefits of registration and so that you get the best out of our website and services. You can unregister at any time by contacting us at the address given above.

  * We may also collect information about you if you enter a competition or post on a message board. If you use our message boards, please remember that any information you put on the message boards is able to be seen by other users of the websites. We do not monitor the message boards.

  * We may collect information about you if you report a problem with our website or services.

  * If you contact us via the mobile version of our Website, we may obtain your telephone number, your carrier’s name, the date and time of our message and similar identifying information.

  * If you contact us for any other reason, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, weblogs and other communication data.

  * We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration purposes.

  * We may also aggregate information about you with information about other visitors to the website in order to identify trends in our business ("Aggregated Data").

Where we store your information

The information that we collect about you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside of the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. In these cases, we require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with this privacy policy.

By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

### What are cookies and why do we use them?

This website uses "cookies". These are small files of data that are downloaded onto your computer when you visit our website. Amongst other things, they allow our website to "remember" your activities on our website and the number of times you have visited. We can use the information stored by cookies to help us to provide you with a better on-line experience. We also use this information to create the Aggregated Data mentioned above.

By agreeing to our terms and conditions and this Privacy Policy and by continuing to use our website you consent to our use of cookies in this manner.

You can set your Internet browser so it will not accept cookies. If you choose not to accept cookies you will still be able to browse our website but you will not be able to take advantage of any of the personalised options, such as registration.

For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie policy below.

### Marketing Communications

Information that we collect about you may be used to send you information about our business, or films or other useful information (for example, newsletters, details of competitions, special offers and promotions and information about latest releases).

When you register with us we will also ask you if you would like to receive information about the products or services of our third party business partners that we think may be of interest to you. We will not send you this information without your consent.

Remember, if you do not want to receive any more information from us all you have to do is contact us at the address at the top of the policy at any time.

### Third Parties

We will not usually pass your information onto any third parties without your consent. We may however pass your information to certain third parties without your consent as follows:

  * We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means IMAX Corporation and its subsidiaries.
  * We may disclose your personal information to third parties who carry out certain services for us. For example, if you win a competition we will pass your information onto a third party who will arrange delivery of your prize.
  * If our business is sold, your information will be passed to the new owner.
  * Where we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our [terms of use](https://www.imax.com/corporate/terms-of-use/) or to protect our rights. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * We may pass Aggregated Data to third parties such as advertisers and business partners to give them a better understanding of our business. However, such information will not identify you personally.
  * Where we pass your information to third parties, we will require them to use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner theatres, distributors, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### Security

We have taken steps to ensure that all personally identifiable information that we collect is secure, including limiting the number of people who can access this information and using electronic security systems. You can help by ensuring that you keep your passwords secret and properly log out of our websites if you have been using them.

### What is "phishing"?

"Phishing" is a scam where fraudsters pretend that they represent well-known companies to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail claiming to be from IMAX that asks you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through e-mail.

### Minors

The website is not intended for the use of any person under the age of 13.  Users between the ages of 13 and 18 must have the consent of their parent or guardian to register as a user.

### Access to your personal information

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information that we hold about you and to have any errors corrected. If you would like to make a request please write to us at the address at the top of this policy enclosing the fee of £5.

### Changes to this Policy

From time to time we may make changes to this policy. We will post a notice of the changes together with the updated policy on the website.

This Policy was last updated on 3 April 2014.
